<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--<string name="toc">
        &lt;!&ndash;### TERMS and CONDITIONS###&ndash;&gt;
        <h1 style="color: #000000; text-align: center;">Terms and Conditions</h1>
<p>THE TERMS OF USE ("\""TERMS"\"" OR "\""AGREEMENT"\"") SET FORTH BELOW, AND UPDATED FROM TIME TO TIME, DESCRIBE THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS THAT SHALL GOVERN YOUR USE OF Grameenphone Ltd's MobiCash MOBILE FINANCIAL SERVICES SYSTEM (THE "\""SERVICES"\"" AND THE "MobiCash SYSTEM", RESPECTIVELY) "\""MobiCash"\"".</p>
<p>BY CLICKING ON THE "\""ACCEPT THE TERMS &amp; CONDITION "\"" BUTTON AND/OR BY DOWNLOADING AND/OR INSTALLING AND/OR ACTIVATING THE MobiCash MOBILE SOFTWARE APPLICATION (THE "\""APPLICATION"\"") AND/OR USING THE APPLICATION AND/OR THE SERVICES, YOU ARE AGREEING TO THE FOLLOWING TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS. TOGETHER WITH THE TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS OF MobiCash.</p>
<p>IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS, REFRAIN FROM DOWNLOADING OR INSTALLING OR ACTIVATING OR USING THE APPLICATION OR THE SERVICES.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h3><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Main Features of the MobiCash App:</span></h3>
<p>Services Offered</p>
<p>The Application offers a range of Services, conducted between users of the MobiCash System,</p>
<p>including the ability to:</p>
<p>Flexi Load Services</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- Perform Flexiload for yourself using your MobiCash wallet balance.</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- Perform Flexiload for any other GP number using your MobiCash wallet balance.</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- You can make your favourite list for quick Flexiload.</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- You can remove a mobile number from favourite list</p>
<h4>Utility BillPay</h4>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- You can pay your Utility bills of GP BillPay Service Partners.</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- Associate or link your Mobile number against a utility account number to get transaction notification</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">or Bill upload notification</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- Cancel an association of Utility account number against your mobile number</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">Account Information &amp; Referrals</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- View your account balances.</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- View up to the last 5 transactions on your accounts.</p>
<p style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;">- Invite or refer any mobile number to download the MobiCash App for use</p>
<h4><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Important Elements in our Terms and Conditions that you should be particularly aware of</span></h4>
<h4><span style="text-decoration: underline;">before using<br /><br /></span></h4>
<h4>Security</h4>
<p>You must take all reasonable precautions to keep safe and prevent fraudulent use of your mobile device and security information.</p>
<p>The precautions include:</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Never writing down or otherwise recording your security details in a way that can be understood by</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">someone else;</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Not choosing security details that may be easy to guess;</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Taking care to ensure that no one hears or sees your security details when you use it;</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Keeping your security details unique to Other (Online or Physical) Banking and the MobiCash App;</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Not disclosing your security details to anyone, including the Law Enforcing Agencies and us;</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Changing your security details frequently</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Keeping your security details and mobile device safe;</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Keeping your device safe &amp; its security along with other financial security detail with in is also your</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">responsibility</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- Once you have logged onto the MobiCash App do not leave your mobile device unattended or let</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">anyone else use your mobile device</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- logging out of the MobiCash App once you have finished using the App services, and in particular</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">not leaving the App running in the background whilst logged in (e.g. whilst multi-tasking, or running</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">other apps);</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">- You will be responsible for all instructions given by you or anyone acting with your authority between</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">when you log onto the MobiCash App until you log off the App.</p>
<h4>Charges</h4>
<p>However, your mobile network operator or any other internet service provider may charge you to access the App and these charges may vary if you access the App when abroad. You will be solely responsible for these usage and charges.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Suspension and Disconnection</h4>
<p>MobiCash reserves the right to suspend or terminate the provision of the Services, at its sole discretion, if you use the wallet for unauthorized purposes or if we suspect the App has been used fraudulently or in an unauthorised way. We may notify you in advance, but may not always be able to in the event of account suspension, for any reason other than use for unauthorized purposes.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Registration</h4>
<p>In order to utilize MobiCash Services, you will be required to create a user wallet by registering your user Mobile number and wallet PIN. As part of the registration process you will receive an OTP (one time password) which will be automatically captured by MobiCash system to allow you to access the MobiCash APP based on your handset device &amp; its operating system's capability. Some devices &amp; version of operating systems may not allow automatic OTP reading &amp; you may have to enter it manually while registering. By registering for the Services or the MobiCash App in your device and creating a user account you represent that you are of legal age and capacity to form a binding contract under applicable law.</p>
<h4>MobiCash Refill</h4>
<p>To avail MobiCash services through MobiCash APP, you need to load balance in your MobiCash wallet. You can load balance on your MobiCash wallet by depositing the desired cash amount with any MobiCash Agent outlet. The cash you load will be deposited in the main MobiCash wallet and will be represented as Balance in your wallet in Bangladeshi Taka.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Redeeming MobiCash balance</h4>
<p>The balance of your MobiCash wallet is not redeemable. You can only consume the balance through paying utility bills or by performing Flexiload to buy Aitime using this APP as an interface only.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Transactions</h4>
<p>Upon loading balance to your MobiCash wallet, you will be able to use MobiCash services through this APP. The MobiCash System will not allow you to transfer balance from your wallet to another wallet. You can only consume the balance through paying utility bills or by purchasing airtime. No Transaction can be cancelled after conducting it. In any event, the Commission paid &amp; tax vat deducted will not be refunded (if any).</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Service Charge</h4>
<p>For BillPay Transaction a Service Charge will be charged at the rate set forth in the Service Charge schedule (the "Service Charges") which is approved by regulatory authority. The applicable service charge will be deducted from your wallet upon conclusion of each Transaction, and the new account balance will appear in the MobiCash System and will be communicated to you by a system message. No service charge will be charged for performing Flexiload and wallet management services such as balance verification or change of PIN code.&#160;</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Maintenance and Support</h4>
<p>As long as you are registered for the Services, you will be entitled to receive for no additional consideration, maintenance and support services for the Services and the Application, in accordance with MobiCash standard terms, by calling the customer service call-center, whose number shall be provided by the Agent and on Grameenphone web site and as may be updated from time to time.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Loss or Theft</h4>
<p>It is your responsibility to keep your PIN code/password away from your mobile phone. Do not write the PIN code on or next to your mobile phone. You may change your PIN code or password at any time through the MobiCash application or by dialling *777# in 'My MobiCash' menu option. &#160;</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Application License</h4>
<p>Software Application; Grant of License : In order to access and use the Services via&#160; your mobile phone or the Internet , and in order to download the Application on your smart-phone, Grameenphone Ltd. grants to you a limited, non-exclusive and revocable license to use the Application as provided herein, solely for the purpose of receiving the Services.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Other Rights and Limitations</h4>
<p>You may not, and may not permit or aid others to, translate, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, update, modify, reproduce, duplicate, copy, distribute or otherwise disseminate all or any part of the Application, or extract or attempt to extract source code from the object code of the Application. The Application is licensed as a single product; you may not separate its component parts for any purpose. You may not make any commercial use of the Application, whether or not for consideration. Upon identification of such attempt or use of your identity to attempt such act may result in legal action from Grameenphone Ltd.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Ownership of Rights</h4>
<p>The Services and the Application and any software used in connection therewith contain proprietary and confidential information. You acknowledge and agree that the Services and the Application are proprietary of Grameenphone Ltd. and its licensors, protected under applicable intellectual property and other laws and international treaties. You further acknowledge and agree that all right, title and interest in and to the Services, the Application and any software therein, including associated intellectual property rights, are and shall remain with Grameenphone Ltd. and its licensors. This Agreement does not convey to you any interest in or to the Services, the Application and any software therein, except for a limited right of use as set forth herein, terminable in accordance with the terms of this Agreement. You will not remove, alter or deface any trademarks or proprietary notices of Grameenphone Ltd or MobiCash brand or of its licensors in the Application.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Privacy&#160;</h4>
<p>In connection with the provision of the Service, Grameenphone will collect and process personal data about you and your use of the Service. Grameenphone's Privacy Statement as amended from time to time is available on the Website. By using our Service, you agree that Grameenphone can use your personal data in accordance with our Privacy Statement and as otherwise set out in any applicable Service Specific Terms. Save as provided hereunder, Grameenphone Ltd. will not share your personal information with unauthorized persons. Adequate safeguards have been put in place to prevent unauthorized access and to ensure confidentiality of your personal information.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Acknowledgement</h4>
<p>You acknowledge that by using the Services, some of your personal information will be passed on to the organization for which you are paying bill or to the person for whom you are purchasing airtime through your wallet, and will be available to any third party involved in the operation of the Services. You also acknowledge that Grameenphone may verify your identity information through publicly available and/or restricted government or election commission databases in order to comply with regulatory requirements. You accept that Grameenphone Ltd. shall have the right to monitor your account usage and may disclose personal information to local law enforcement or investigative agencies or any competent regulatory or governmental agencies to assist in the prevention, detection or prosecution of money laundering activities, fraud or other criminal activities.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Security</h4>
<p>Grameenphone shall take all required and reasonable measures to ensure the security of the MobiCash System. However, due to the virtual nature of the system and all of its components, which are exposed to security risks by their nature, including disclosure or modification of data installed on the system by unauthorized persons, a security risk exists. You acknowledge the existence of such security risk involved in the use of the MobiCash system.</p>
<p>&#160;&#160;</p>
<h4>Warranty; Limitation of Liability</h4>
<p>GRAMEENPHONE LTD PROVIDES THE APPLICATION AND SERVICES "AS IS" AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OR CONDITION, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY. MobiCash DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE APPLICATION AND SERVICES SHALL BE ERROR-FREE, THAT THEY SHALL OPERATE UNINTERRUPTED OR THAT THEY SHALL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS.</p>
<p>MobiCash DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<p>Not withstanding anything herein to the contrary, Grameenphone 's sole and cumulative liability to you or any third party for any loss, cost or damage resulting from any claims, demands or actions arising out of or relating to these Terms and/or your use of the Application and/or the Services shall not exceed the maximum wallet balance immediately preceding the occurrence of the event giving rise to the applicable loss, cost or damage. In no event shall MobiCash be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, punitive, or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, misconduct of agents; technical problems of kiosks; Transactions made to unintended recipients or in incorrect amounts due to the input of incorrect information by you; transactions made from your account by an unauthorized third party who passes all identity and verification checks; any fraud, deception or misrepresentations by any agent; any damages resulting from a recipient's decision not to accept or record a Transaction made by you through the MobiCash System; failure of any other telecommunications or data transmission system other than the MobiCash System; any result of any acts of government or authority, or force majeure; damages for loss of profits, revenue, goodwill, use, data, electronically transmitted requests or other economic advantage (even if MobiCash has been advised of the possibility of such damages), however caused and regardless of the theory of liability, whether in contract (including fundamental breach), tort (including negligence) or otherwise, arising out of or related to the use of or the inability to use the Application and/or the Services for any reason. Some states may not allow the limitation or exclusion of liability for indirect, incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Intellectual Property Rights</h4>
<p>All rights, title to and interest in the Service (excluding User Content) are and will remain the exclusive property of Grameenphone Ltd. The Service and its content are protected by copyright and other intellectual property rights in the country you reside as well as foreign countries. Except for the limited, personal, non-exclusive, non-transferrable and revocable license granted to you for the sole purpose of your use of the Service in compliance with the Terms, you are not granted any ownership of or license to any intellectual property rights in our Service or in the content owned by us our partners that you access through the Service.</p>
<p>The trademarks, logos, domain names and any other similar signs or symbols which are displayed on the Website or as part of the Service are the registered and unregistered marks of Grameenphone Ltd.. Nothing in the Terms grants you the right to use any such marks.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<p>All rights, title to and interest in User Content submitted by you will remain the exclusive property of you and/or your licensors. By submitting User Content, you grant Grameenphone Ltd, or must procure that your licensors grant Grameenphone Ltd, a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, transferrable, sub-licensable, irrevocable and worldwide license to use, reproduce, store, modify, distribute, publish and create derivative works of such User Content for any purpose, commercial or otherwise. You represent and warrant that you own any User Content submitted by you or that you otherwise are entitled to submit such User Content and to grant us such license.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Indemnity</h4>
<p>You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Grameenphone Ltd (including, but not limited to, affiliated companies and their contractors, officers, directors and employees) and its partners from all claims, liabilities and expenses (including reasonable attorney's fees) that arise from your misuse of the Service in breach of the Terms or applicable laws.</p>
<p>Grameenphone Ltd reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you. You shall cooperate in good faith with Grameenphone Ltd in asserting any available defenses.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Termination</h4>
<p>You may stop using our Service. You may uninstall the MobiCash Application from your device. This will however not effect the validity of your MobiCash wallet. Grameenphone Ltd may also stop providing Service to you, or add limits to your Service. If you act in breach of the Terms or applicable laws, your right to use the Service and access its content will in any event immediately, without notice, terminate without refund of any fees.</p>
<h4>Legal Compliance</h4>
<p>You shall comply with all applicable domestic and international laws, statutes, ordinances and regulations regarding your use of the Services as well as MobiCash Application referred here as "\""MobiCash App"\"" or "\""MobiCash APP"\"" or "\""APP"\"".</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Governing Law and Jurisdiction; Litigation Costs</h4>
<p>This Agreement shall be construed and governed in accordance with the laws of country of Bangladesh and the competent courts of the Bangladesh shall have sole and exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute under this Agreement. If any action is brought by either party to this Agreement against the other party regarding the subject matter hereof, the prevailing party shall be entitled to recover, in addition to any other relief granted, reasonable attorney fees and expenses of litigation.</p>
<h4>Miscellaneous</h4>
<p>Should any term of this Agreement be declared void or unenforceable by any court of competent jurisdiction, such declaration shall have no effect on the remaining terms hereof. This Agreement represents the entire agreement between you and MobiCash with respect to the subject matter hereof and they supersede any prior proposal, representation, or understanding between the parties. All provisions of these Terms which by their subject matter should survive termination shall survive termination including suspension of your wallet and/or rights to use the Services or any part thereof, including without limitation provisions pertaining to ownership, intellectual property, warranty and liability. The failure of either party to enforce any rights granted hereunder or to take action against the other party in the event of any breach hereunder shall not be deemed a waiver by that party as to subsequent enforcement of rights or subsequent actions in the event of future breaches.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>How to Complain</h4>
<p>If we do not deliver the standard of service you expect, or if you think we have made a mistake, please let us know. We will investigate the situation and, if necessary, set about putting matters right as quickly as possible. Where appropriate we will also take steps to prevent a recurrence. To lodge your complaints please call to our Call center. Our Call center number is 1200. This Call Center is open from 8am -10pm. To call to our Call Center standard call Charges will be applied as per BTRC directives.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>Service Charges</h4>
<p>BRTC approved standard Service Charges for Bill Payment from MobiCash wallet regardless of user interface (USSD or App) are as follows.</p>
<p>Bill Amount Service Charge Bill Amount Service Charge</p>
<p><strong>&#160;</strong></p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>
<p><strong>Bill Amount</strong></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><strong>Service Charge</strong></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><strong>Bill Amount</strong></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><strong>Service Charge</strong></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Upto BDT 400</span></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BDT 5</span></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BDT 1501 TO BDT 5000</span></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BDT 15</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BDT 401 to BDT 1500</span></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BDT 10</span></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BDT 5001 or more</span></p>
</td>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BDT 25</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>Promotional Service charges may be charged for this service time to time following standard process of Intimation to Regulator which is BTRC. Promotional offer may vary based on user interface &amp; GP reserves the sole right to decide on that. This may or may not be communicated to you over this interface. You may get the information from general communication or information centres or relevant website.</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<h4>General</h4>
<p>For more information please visit:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.grameenphone.com/personal/digital-services/mobile-financial-services">http://www.grameenphone.com/personal/digital-services/mobile-</a><a href="http://www.grameenphone.com/personal/digital-services/mobile-financial-services">financial-services</a></p>
<p>&#160;</p>
</string>-->
</resources>